d_affinia_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=164, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=3, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=224, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Affina Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Affina Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('7:18 AM', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('7:18 AM', 'TIME'), ('Affina Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=68, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Affina Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affina Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=146, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Navy Pier', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Navy Pier', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_affinia_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=250, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('7:30 in the morning', 'TIME'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('7:30 in the morning', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=180, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=72, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_affinia_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=114, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('$700', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$700', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=186, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=93, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago!', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago!', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_affinia_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=68, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=168, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=280, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=3, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=113, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_affinia_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=145, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=90, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Friday', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=331, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('New York City', 'LOCATION'), ('Affinia Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New York City', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=390, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Affinia Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('morning every morning', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('Affinia Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('morning every morning', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=83, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=2, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=2, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('$49', 'MONEY'), ('$10', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$49', 'MONEY'), ('$10', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_affinia_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=112, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('$49', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$49', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=188, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel Allegro Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hotel Allegro Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=112, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=203, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel Allegro Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hotel Allegro Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=205, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hotel Allegro Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sandy D.', 'PERSON')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hotel Allegro Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sandy D.', 'PERSON')}
d_allegro_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=56, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_allegro_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=134, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=2, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago Loop', 'LOCATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago Loop', 'LOCATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}
d_allegro_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=206, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=6, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=3, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=3, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME')}
d_allegro_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=154, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_allegro_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=77, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_allegro_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=388, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=237, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=108, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('two cents', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('two cents', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=95, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Jacuzzi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('summer', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('summer', 'DATE'), ('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Jacuzzi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=151, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_allegro_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=183, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hotel Allegro', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=301, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=2, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=2, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('September 2', 'DATE'), ('5, 2011', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('September 2', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('5, 2011', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_allegro_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=148, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_allegro_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=74, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_allegro_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=218, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Kimpton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kimpton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Kimpton', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_allegro_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=144, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_amalfi_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=60, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=218, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_amalfi_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=165, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=4, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=3, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('LA', 'LOCATION'), ('San Francisco', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('LA', 'LOCATION'), ('San Francisco', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=134, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_amalfi_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=122, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=152, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_amalfi_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=230, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=125, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=250, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Marriott', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Marriott', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_amalfi_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=96, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=63, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_amalfi_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=260, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_amalfi_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=137, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=345, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=118, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_amalfi_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=59, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=103, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_amalfi_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=307, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_amalfi_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=121, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_amalfi_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=255, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Keefer', 'PERSON')}, unique_occurrences: {('Amalfi', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Keefer', 'PERSON'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=50, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_ambassador_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=214, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Gold Coast', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Gold Coast', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_ambassador_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=292, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chigaco', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chigaco', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=341, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=323, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('$15', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$15', 'MONEY')}
d_ambassador_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=229, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('summer', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('summer', 'DATE')}
d_ambassador_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=129, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_ambassador_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=315, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('CRT', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('CRT', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('afternoon', 'TIME')}
d_ambassador_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=145, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('two night', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('two night', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=127, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=85, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Ambassador East Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('last month', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('last month', 'DATE'), ('Ambassador East Hotel', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=105, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_ambassador_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=226, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Abassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Air', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('August', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Abassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Air', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=106, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('$10', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$10', 'MONEY')}
d_ambassador_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=189, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Downtown Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Downtown Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=107, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('35 dollars', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('35 dollars', 'MONEY')}
d_ambassador_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=92, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_ambassador_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=119, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('$10', 'MONEY'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('weekend', 'DATE'), ('$10', 'MONEY')}
d_ambassador_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=171, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Ambassador East Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_ambassador_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=131, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_conrad_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=117, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=371, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=3, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad', 'PERSON')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad', 'PERSON'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=110, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=173, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_conrad_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=257, total_entity_count=6, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=3, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Windy City', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Hotel and Resort', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Hotel and Resort', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Hotel and Resort', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Windy City', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=343, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_conrad_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=291, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=6, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=2, PERCENT=0, DATE=2, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=2, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('three hundred dollars', 'MONEY'), ('three hundred dollars', 'MONEY'), ('midnight each evening', 'TIME'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('three hundred dollars', 'MONEY'), ('midnight each evening', 'TIME'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=150, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Windy City', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Windy City', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=378, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=198, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=100, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_conrad_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=54, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=121, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Michelin', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Michelin', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_conrad_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=125, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago Conrad', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago Conrad', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=452, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=4, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=308, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Charlie Sheen', 'PERSON')}, unique_occurrences: {('Charlie Sheen', 'PERSON'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_conrad_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=157, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_conrad_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=172, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_conrad_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=350, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=7, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=4, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Conrad Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Hotels', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Hotels', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_conrad_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=439, total_entity_count=6, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=3, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('September', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('September', 'DATE'), ('Conrad Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=70, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('American Girl Place', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$100', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$100', 'MONEY'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('American Girl Place', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=101, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=168, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chacago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chacago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=173, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=2, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=2, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$500', 'MONEY'), ('$20', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$20', 'MONEY'), ('$500', 'MONEY'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=164, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=5, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=2, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=2, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('$14.95', 'MONEY'), ('$51.00', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$51.00', 'MONEY'), ('$14.95', 'MONEY'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=168, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Western Suburbs of Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Western Suburbs of Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=73, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=126, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=297, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=194, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=231, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=181, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=212, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=228, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=82, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=125, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=121, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('New York', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('night', 'TIME'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New York', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=317, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_fairmont_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=230, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Doc Martens', 'PERSON')}, unique_occurrences: {('Doc Martens', 'PERSON'), ('Fairmont Chicago Millennium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_fairmont_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=276, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millemmium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('midnight', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('Fairmont Chicago Millemmium Park Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('midnight', 'TIME')}
d_hardrock_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=149, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=109, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('last year', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('last year', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=85, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_hardrock_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=251, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=79, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=49, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=68, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('250 dollars', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('250 dollars', 'MONEY'), ('Hard Rock Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hardrock_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=287, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=77, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=81, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=477, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=5, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=131, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hardrock_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=163, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('$300', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$300', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=231, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$10', 'MONEY'), ('July', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('July', 'DATE'), ('Hard Rock Hotel Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$10', 'MONEY')}
d_hardrock_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=213, total_entity_count=6, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=2, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('night', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=254, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=282, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=155, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=261, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hard Rock Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hardrock_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=89, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=270, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Schicago Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Schicago Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hilton_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=81, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_hilton_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=197, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=147, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hilton_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=208, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=267, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('two weeks later', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('two weeks later', 'DATE')}
d_hilton_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=784, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('AAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('AAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hilton_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=125, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=3, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=3, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$200', 'MONEY'), ('$40', 'MONEY'), ('$20', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$40', 'MONEY'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$20', 'MONEY'), ('$200', 'MONEY')}
d_hilton_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=129, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=5, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=3, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago!', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago!', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('night', 'TIME')}
d_hilton_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=115, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=106, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hilton_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=159, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$10', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$10', 'MONEY')}
d_hilton_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=151, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=4, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$43', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$43', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=197, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=5, LOCATION=1, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("Kitty O'Sheas", 'PERSON'), ('July', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('July', 'DATE'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("Kitty O'Sheas", 'PERSON'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=126, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=134, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=230, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hilton_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=408, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('two days later', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('two days later', 'DATE'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hilton_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=138, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Customer Service', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Customer Service', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hilton_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=259, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('a week earlier', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('a week earlier', 'DATE')}
d_homewood_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=143, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=127, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_homewood_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=195, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('University of Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Windy City', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('10th anniversary', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Windy City', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('10th anniversary', 'DATE'), ('University of Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_homewood_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=150, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('last week', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('last week', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=170, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=273, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('morning', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('morning', 'TIME'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_homewood_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=197, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=392, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ESPN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$5', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$5', 'MONEY'), ('ESPN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_homewood_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=162, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=167, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_homewood_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=162, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_homewood_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=159, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('summer', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('summer', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=153, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago Downtown', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago Downtown', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_homewood_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=133, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=2, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('1960', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('1960', 'DATE'), ('Hilton Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hilton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('morning', 'TIME')}
d_homewood_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=218, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Chicago Downtown', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Chicago Downtown', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=239, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('$60-a-night', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('$60-a-night', 'MONEY'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=370, total_entity_count=7, total_unique_entity_count=6, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=2, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=3, unique_MONEY=2, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("McDonald's", 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$259', 'MONEY'), ('$30', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("McDonald's", 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('$259', 'MONEY'), ('$30', 'MONEY')}
d_homewood_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=251, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=3, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Michigan Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Group Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Michigan Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Group Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_homewood_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=81, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_homewood_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=245, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Downtown Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hilton Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hilton Homewood Suites', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Downtown Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=94, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=166, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Real House Wives of New Jersey', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Real House Wives of New Jersey', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hyatt_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=88, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hyatt_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=138, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_hyatt_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=262, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Army', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Army', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hyatt_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=197, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_hyatt_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=255, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=120, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=363, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=122, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_hyatt_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=112, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=158, total_entity_count=9, total_unique_entity_count=7, LOCATION=3, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=3, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=2, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sam', 'PERSON'), ('$20', 'MONEY'), ('$75', 'MONEY'), ('$20', 'MONEY'), ('weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Sam', 'PERSON'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$75', 'MONEY'), ('$20', 'MONEY')}
d_hyatt_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=141, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=1, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=1, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Gideon', 'PERSON')}, unique_occurrences: {('Gideon', 'PERSON'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=157, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_hyatt_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=113, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=106, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('night', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('night', 'TIME')}
d_hyatt_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=160, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=3, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=3, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatts', 'LOCATION'), ('Hiltons', 'LOCATION'), ('3 a.m.', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('3 a.m.', 'TIME'), ('Hiltons', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatts', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=93, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_8.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=107, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_hyatt_9.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=218, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Hyatt Regency Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Hyatt Regency Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_1.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=162, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('morning', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('morning', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_10.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=127, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_11.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=141, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Intercontinental Chicago Magnificent Mile', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Intercontinental Chicago Magnificent Mile', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_intercontinental_12.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=59, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('InterContinental Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('InterContinental Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_13.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=184, total_entity_count=9, total_unique_entity_count=8, LOCATION=2, PERSON=3, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=2, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=2, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=2, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Louisville', 'LOCATION'), ('Nina', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Erin', 'PERSON'), ('Erin', 'PERSON'), ('Mrs. Scott Grander', 'PERSON'), ('8:00', 'TIME'), ('8:15', 'TIME'), ('$300', 'MONEY')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('8:15', 'TIME'), ('Erin', 'PERSON'), ('Louisville', 'LOCATION'), ('Mrs. Scott Grander', 'PERSON'), ('$300', 'MONEY'), ('Nina', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('8:00', 'TIME')}
d_intercontinental_14.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=140, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Intercontinental Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Intercontinental Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_intercontinental_15.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=226, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=1, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=1, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('InterContinental Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('two night', 'TIME')}, unique_occurrences: {('InterContinental Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('two night', 'TIME'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_16.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=194, total_entity_count=4, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('InterContinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('InterContinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('InterContinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_17.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=262, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_18.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=171, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('InterContinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('InterContinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_19.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=57, total_entity_count=0, total_unique_entity_count=0, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {}, unique_occurrences: {}
d_intercontinental_2.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=264, total_entity_count=3, total_unique_entity_count=3, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=2, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=2, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('weekend of Sept. 17-18', 'DATE'), ('2011', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('2011', 'DATE'), ('weekend of Sept. 17-18', 'DATE'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_20.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=62, total_entity_count=1, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_3.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=94, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=0, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=2, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=0, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=2, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('International Chicago Magnificent Mile', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Google', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Google', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('International Chicago Magnificent Mile', 'ORGANIZATION')}
d_intercontinental_4.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=228, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=1, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=0, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=0, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_5.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=405, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=5, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=3, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=2, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=3, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Michigan Ave.', 'LOCATION'), ('Intercontinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Housekeeping Department', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Intercontinental Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('Housekeeping Department', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Intercontinental Chicago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Michigan Ave.', 'LOCATION'), ('Intercontinental Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_6.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=131, total_entity_count=5, total_unique_entity_count=4, LOCATION=2, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=1, PERCENT=0, DATE=1, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=1, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=1, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('$18', 'MONEY'), ('holiday weekend', 'DATE')}, unique_occurrences: {('$18', 'MONEY'), ('holiday weekend', 'DATE'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
d_intercontinental_7.txt, deceptive, n, word_count=269, total_entity_count=2, total_unique_entity_count=2, LOCATION=1, PERSON=0, ORGANIZATION=1, MONEY=0, PERCENT=0, DATE=0, TIME=0, unique_LOCATION=1, unique_PERSON=0, unique_ORGANIZATION=1, unique_MONEY=0, unique_PERCENT=0, unique_DATE=0, unique_TIME=0, occurrences: {('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('InterContinental Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION')}, unique_occurrences: {('InterContinental Chicago Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')}
